avishya.com 2016-06-28

# Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
---  
Welcome to Avishya.com. This section pertains to the Privacy Policy of the website and native mobile applications. We would like to inform that our privacy policy is subject to change without intimation and you shall be required to review the same regularly.

The protection and security of your personal information is one of Avishya.com's top priorities. This Privacy Policy discloses Avishya.com's practice with respect to the information collected from the users of the Website.  By using the Website you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy as well as the Website Terms of Use. By accessing or using the Website you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in any manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy extends to both, users who visit the Website but do not transact business on the Website as well as users who are registered on the Website or native mobile applications. "Personal Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact or locate the person, to whom such information pertains including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, identification number, credit card information etc.  

**What customer information does Avishya.com collect?**  
1) | Your contact details such as customer name, email address, Avishya.com account password, phone number and shipping address  
2) | Your previous orders and transactions including the product and pricing details, the date of purchase, payment history, etc.  
3) | Cookies:  Cookies are pieces of data stored by a website within a browser than enable the browser to remember information specific to a given user such as clicking particular links, viewing specific product, logging in or viewing specific pages on our site.  The cookies however do not store any personal information including name and contact details. All leading internet companies use cookies and you can set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent to you.  Deciding whether you want to accept a cookie or not, is totally up to you.  
4) | Your session log information on our site which includes your navigation within the website, source of traffic, IP address (from which we can approximately determine your location), browser type, device type, operating system date of request, etc.  
5) | Third party sign-in information shared on our website such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, etc.  
6) | Information from optional online surveys on our or third party sites (posted by avishya.com) which may include demographic information (like gender, age, income) as well as product and service preferences of users.  
7) | Email communication by any user or customer directly with avishya.com such as product enquiry, order and transaction related information, disputes or complaints etc.  
8) | Avishya.com DOES NOT hold (or) store your banking details such as credit card number, cardholder name, expiration date and CVV or other information as required for internet banking or other payment instruments. This information is held by our various payment gateway partners (PayU, Razor Pay, Paypal etc.).  All our partners are “Verisign secured” and “PCI-Compliant” Gateways.  Therefore, your information is assured of the highest standards of safety and security.  
9) | User Generated content on the website shared by users via reviews, blogs, online chat or instant messaging, forums, etc. are not considered as personal information and are not subject to the terms of this privacy policy  
  |   |   |    
**How does Avishya.com use customer information?**    
Avishya.com does not allow any unauthorized persons or organizations to use any information that Avishya.com may collect from you through the website.  However, Avishya.com is not responsible for any information collected or shared or used by any other third party website due to your browser settings.  
1) | We only collect user / customer information as required to conduct our business and to enable us to provide the best services to our customers.  We do not rent or sell our customer information  
2) | Information collected from you will be used as follows:  
  | a. | Customer Information will be shared with our subsidiaries, affiliates and partners who are involved in delivering the products /services offered in our website to you  
  | b. | We use some of the user information given by you to understand customer behavior and thus offer products / services that are more relevant to you  
  | c. | Information obtained from users will also be used in an aggregated form to create reports and compile demographic profiles for our business & marketing activities  
  | d. | To inform you about your order and shipping status, deals, new launches, information about the products you have purchased and other promotional /informational content.  You have the option to opt out of all such services except for order related information  
  | e. | We also use session logs & traffic flow information to understand how users are interacting with our website. This will also be used by us to understand customer preferences, buying patterns and behavior at an aggregate level  
  | f. | We will need to use user information as required in case of legal disputes or other legal processes: to comply with any statutory or regulatory requirements, detect and protect against error, fraud and other criminal or illegal activity; prevent abuse of our services and prevent violation of rights of third parties, other users or the general public  
  | g. | We have implemented Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (Google Display Network Impression Reporting, Doubleclick Campaign Manager Integration and Google Analytics Demographics & Interest Reporting).  Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings  
  | h. | We, along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.  
  | No products or services available on the website are directed toward children.  Avishya.com does not knowingly collect personal information from children or sell its products to children  
3) | Avishya.com provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account. To remove your contact information from Avishya.com, please write to us at help@avishya.com  
4) | Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: help@avishya.com  
      
BY USING THE WEBSITE OR NATIVE MOBILE APPLICATIONS, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AVISHYA.COM RESERVES THE RIGHT, IN OUR SOLE DISCRETION, TO CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD OR DELETE PORTIONS OF THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME.  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to [Contact Us] through our Website or write to us at help@avishya.com
